//Buildings
30000=Hall of Lord
30001=Mint
30002=Aureustone Mill
30003=Wall
30004=Camp
30005=Treasure House
30006=Covenant Tower
30007=Cellar
30008=Town Hall
30009=Parthenon
30010=Prancing Horse Tavern
30011=Blacksmith's Shop
30012=Monument
30013=Auro Ruins
                
//Building Description             
31000=Hall of Lord is the central of a city, in which heros can be viewed. By upgrading Hall of Lord, other building's level cap can be increased, new buildings may open as well.     
31001=Mint produces gold coins,  and output of gold can be increased by upgrading Mint.         
31002=Aureustone produces Aureustone, and output of Aureustone can be increased by upgrading Aureustone.
31003=Wall provides defensive towers, which may help with defensive battles. The number of towers and Damage can be increased by upgrading Wall. Formations of defensive battles can also be set in Wall.
31004=Soldiers are recruit and stationed in Camp. Number of soldiers can be increased by upgrading Camp.   
31005=Gold coin and Aureustone can be stored in Treasure House, and the capacity can be raised by upgrading it.    
31006=You can establish or join in a Union by owning Covenant Tower. Union Technology Level cap can be increased by upgrading Covenant Tower.
31007=Cellar may reduce the loss of  resources when the city's plundered. The higher level it reaches, the more resources may be protected.     
31008=Town Hall will increase the output of the gold coin and Aureustone. The higher its level is, the higher the output is. 
31009=Parthenon may output hero exp. The higher its level is, the faster its output is. All heros can also be viewed in Parthenon.
31010=Prancing Horse Tavern is where you can recruit the heros. The higher its level is, the more card you can draw for free per day, and the greater the chances to draw high quality cards.
31011=Blacksmith's Shop is the place to upgrade the units. Units Level cap can be increased as you upgrade the Blacksmith's Shop.
31012=Achievements and ranking list can be viewed in Monument.
31013=The place to foster heros.


663500010=Full level reached
663500011=Time
663500012=Price
663500013=Upgrade
663500014=Effects
663500015=Building Level Cap:
663500016=Potential Level Cap:
663500017=Production:
663500018=Storage Cap:
663500019=Number of Tower:
663500020=Tower Damage:
663500021=Reserve Forces Cap:
663500022=Gold Storage:
663500023=Aureustone Storage:
663500024=Minimum Gold:
663500025=Minimum Aureustone: 
663500026=Gold Production:
663500027=Aureustone Production:
663500028=Exp Accumulation speed:
663500029=Total Exp Cap:
663500030=Free Recruit Limit:
663500031=Luck Value:
663500032=Army improvement Level Limit:
663500033=Army Evolvement Level Limit:


66350001=Speed up
66350002=Cancel
66350003=upgrade
66350004=Access
66350005=Achievement
66350006=Illustration
66350007=Rankings
66350008=Move
66350009=Under crazy development！
66350010=Billboards


663531000=Hall of Lord is the central of a city, in which heroes can be viewed. By upgrading Hall of Lord, other building's level cap can be increased, new buildings may open as well.
663531001=Mint produces gold coins,  and output of gold can be increased by upgrading Mint. 
663531002=Aureustone produces Aureustone, and output of Aureustone can be increased by upgrading Aureustone.
663531003=Wall provides defensive towers, which may help with defensive battles. The number of towers and Damage can be increased by upgrading Wall. Formations of defensive battles can also be set in Wall.
663531004=Soldiers are recruited and stationed in Camp. Number of soldiers can be increased by upgrading Camp.
663531005=Gold coin and Aureustone can be stored in Treasure House, and the capacity can be raised by upgrading it.
663531006=You can raise the chance to acquire Union Items by upgrading Covenant Tower.
663531007=Cellar may reduce the loss of resources when the city's plundered. The higher level it reaches, the more resources may be protected. 
663531008=Town Hall will increase the output of the gold coin and Aureustone. The higher its level is, the higher the output is. 
663531009=Parthenon outputs hero exp.  The Output speed and Storage Cap will increase by upgrading  Parthenon.
663531010=Prancing Horse Tavern is where you can recruit the heroes. The higher its level is, the more card you can draw for free per day, and the greater the chances to draw high quality cards.
663531011=Blacksmith's Shop is the place to upgrade the units. Units’ Level cap can be increased as you upgrade the Blacksmith's Shop.
663531012=Achievements and Illustrations can be viewed in Monument.
663531013=Heroes' Improvement Cap will increase by Upgrading Auro Ruins, you can also evolve Heroes' Appearance when it achieves certain Level.

